Guide to the Oregonian photographs collection circa 1850-1984
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Portland, 1884-1983; Series C
  - "Learn-to-Swim" Campaign (Box-folder 62/17)
    Annual event hosted by the Oregonian.
  - Lents District (Box-folder 62/18)
  - Lents Park (Box-folder 62/19)
  - Lewis & Clark Exposition, 1905 (Box-folder 62/20)
  - Lewis Building (Box-folder 62/21)
    Located at SW 4th and Oak.
  - Lewis Building (Box-folder 62/22)
    Located at 13th and Washington.
  - Lewis Home (Box-folder 62/23)
  - Libby, McNeill & Libby (Box-folder 62/24)
  - Liberty House (Box-folder 62/25)
  - Liberty Temple, circa 1918 (Box-folder 62/26)
  - Liberty Theatre (Box-folder 62/27)
  - Libraries (1) (Box-folder 62/28)
  - Libraries (2) (Box-folder 62/29)
  - Lightning Bus Fire, 1956 May 28 (Box-folder 62/30)
    Incident in which lightning struck a bus, leading to 16 injuries. Mostly photographs of the injured and of witnesses.
  - Lillis-Albina Park (Box-folder 62/31)
  - Lincoln Building (Box-folder 62/32)
  - Lincoln Day Celebrations (Box-folder 62/33)
  - Lincoln Memorial Cemetery (Box-folder 62/34)
  - Lincoln Savings & Loan Association (Box-folder 62/35)
  - Lindsay Building (Box-folder 63/1)
  - Lions Club (Box-folder 63/2)
  - Lipman, Wolfe & Co. (Box-folder 63/3)
  - Lloyd A. Fry Roofing Co. (Box-folder 63/4)
  - Lloyd Building (Box-folder 63/5)
  - Lloyd Center (1) (Box-folder 63/6)
    Includes photographs and conceptula art of the area when it was known as Lloyd's Addition.
  - Lloyd Center (2) (Box-folder 63/7)
  - Lloyd Golf Club (Box-folder 63/8)
  - Lloyd Plaza (Box-folder 63/9)
  - Logus Block (Box-folder 63/10)
  - Lone Fir Cemetery (Box-folder 63/11)
  - Longshoremen's Strike Commemorations (Box-folder 63/12)
    Gatherings to honor those killed in confrontation during the 1934 strike.
  - Loomis Armored Car Co. (Box-folder 63/13)
  - Los Angeles-Seattle Motor Express, Inc. (Box-folder 63/14)
  - Louise Home for Girls (Box-folder 63/15)
  - Lovejoy Fountain Park (Box-folder 63/16)
  - Low-Income Family Emergency Center (LIFE Center) (Box-folder 63/17)
  - Loyalty Building (Box-folder 63/18)
  - Lucia Brides (Box-folder 63/19)
  - Lumber Manufacturers, Inc. (Box-folder 63/20)
  - Lutheran Family Services (Box-folder 63/21)
  - Lutheran Good Samaritan Home for the Aged (Box-folder 63/22)
  - Lynn Kirby Ford (Box-folder 63/23)
  - Lyric Theater (Box-folder 63/24)
  - M & M Woodworking Co. (Box-folder 63/25)
  - M. Seller Building (Box-folder 63/26)
  - Maccabees' Home (Box-folder 63/27)
  - Mack Trucks, Inc. (Box-folder 63/28)
  - Macleay Park (Box-folder 64/1)
  - Madison Tower (Box-folder 64/2)
  - Magic Circle (Box-folder 64/3)
  - Malarkey Paper Co. (Box-folder 64/4)
  - Manley Center (Box-folder 64/5)
    Also called Helen Kelly Manley Center
  - Mann Home (Box-folder 64/6)
    Residence for seniors.
  - Marble Palace (Box-folder 64/7)
  - March of Dimes Walkathons (Box-folder 64/8)
  - Marian Congress, 1934 August (Box-folder 64/9)
  - Marine Electric Co. (Box-folder 64/10)
  - Marks Home (Box-folder 64/11)
    Residence of Morris Marks.
  - Marquam Building (Box-folder 64/12)
  - Marquam II Building (Box-folder 64/13)
  - Marquam Hills District (Box-folder 64/14)
  - Martha Gatke Murder Case, 1924 April (Box-folder 64/15)
    Image showing the path the killer took before entering the Gatke residence.
  - Masonic Temples (Box-folder 64/16)
    Includes photographs of the Masonic Temple that later became the Portland Art Museum's Mark Building
  - Maternity Brothers (Box-folder 64/17)
  - May Hardware Co. (Box-folder 64/18)
  - Mayflower Dairy Plant (Box-folder 64/19)
  - McCormick SS Co. (Box-folder 64/20)
  - McCracken Bros. Motor Freight Co. (Box-folder 64/21)
  - MacMarr Stores (Box-folder 64/22)
  - Meadowland Dairy (Box-folder 64/23)
  - Meadowlark Park (Box-folder 64/24)
  - Meier & Frank Co. (Box-folder 64/25)
  - Memorial Coliseum (Box-folder 64/26)
  - Memorial Day Celebrations (Box-folder 64/27)
  - Memorial Park Development, 1932 (Box-folder 64/28)
    Photograph of model showing proposed park near Pennoyer Park.
  - Men's Garden Clubs of America Convention, 1968 June (Box-folder 64/29)
  - Mennonite Volunteer Service Center (Box-folder 64/30)
  - Merchants' Trust Building (Box-folder 64/31)
  - Metro Youth (Box-folder 64/32)
  - Metropolitan Printing Co. (Box-folder 64/33)
  - Metropolitan Service Co. (Box-folder 64/34)
  - Military Order of the Cootie, Portland Pup Tent #1 (Box-folder 64/35)
    Group photograph of Veterans' Hospital patients aided by the organization.
  - Miss City of Roses (Box-folder 64/36)
  - Miss Portland (Box-folder 64/37)
  - Miss Tan Portland (Box-folder 64/38)
  - Mobil Oil Co. (Box-folder 65/1)
  - Mobil Mart (Box-folder 65/2)
  - Mobile Health Unit (Box-folder 65/3)
  - Mobilift Corp. (Box-folder 65/4)
  - Mock's Bottom (Box-folder 65/5)
  - Mock's Crest (Box-folder 65/6)
  - Model Cities Program (Box-folder 65/7)
  - Molded Container Corp. (Box-folder 65/8)
  - Molded Fiberglass & Plastics, Inc. (Box-folder 65/9)
  - Monarch Forge & Machine Co. (Box-folder 65/10)
  - Monastery of the Precious Blood (Box-folder 65/11)
  - Montgomery Ward & Co. (Box-folder 65/12)
  - Montis Boarding House (Box-folder 65/13)
  - Morgan Building (Box-folder 65/14)
  - Morgan's Alley (Box-folder 65/15)
  - Morris P. Kirk & Son (Box-folder 65/16)
  - Morrison Center for Youth & Family Services (Box-folder 65/17)
  - Morrison Street Development (Box-folder 65/18)
  - Motels (Box-folder 65/19)
  - Mount Calvary Cemetery (Box-folder 65/20)
  - Mt. Hood Chemical Corp. (Box-folder 65/21)
  - Mt. Scott Community Center (Box-folder 65/22)
  - Mt. Scott Park (Box-folder 65/23)
  - Mt. Tabor (Box-folder 65/24)
  - Mt. Tabor Park (Box-folder 65/25)
  - Mt. Tabor Reservoir (Box-folder 65/26)
  - Mu Phi Epsilon (Box-folder 65/27)
  - Multiple Sclerosis Society of Oregon (Box-folder 65/28)
  - Multnomah Athletic Club (Box-folder 65/29)
  - Multnomah Better Housing Campaign (Box-folder 65/30)
  - Multnomah Center (Box-folder 65/31)
  - Multnomah College (Box-folder 65/32)
    Currently known as Multnomah University.
  - Multnomah County Animal Control (Box-folder 65/33)
  - Multnomah County Commission (Box-folder 65/34)
  - Multnomah County Courthouse (Box-folder 65/35)
  - Multnomah County Exposition Center (Box-folder 65/36)
    Also known as Pacific International Livestock Exposition Center.
  - Multnomah County Extension Service (Box-folder 65/37)
  - Multnomah County Fair (Box-folder 66/1)
  - Multnomah County Health & Education Building (Box-folder 66/2)
  - Multnomah County Intermediate Education District (Box-folder 66/3)
  - Multnomah County Juvenile Home (Box-folder 66/4)
  - Multnomah County Medical Society (Box-folder 66/5)
  - Multnomah County Morgue (Box-folder 66/6)
  - Multnomah County Register Office (Box-folder 66/7)
  - Multnomah County Sheriff's Office (Box-folder 66/8)
  - Multnomah County Task Force Work Program (Box-folder 66/9)
  - Multnomah County Tax Department (Box-folder 66/10)
  - Multnomah Golf Club (Box-folder 66/11)
  - Mulnomah Kennel Club (Box-folder 66/12)
  - Multnomah Stadium (Box-folder 66/13)
  - Multnomah Wheelmen Lowjinks, 1896 June 21 (Box-folder 66/14)
    Group photo.
  - Municipal Courts (Box-folder 66/15)
  - Murlark Hall (Box-folder 66/16)
  - Myasthenia Gravis Foundation, Oregon Chapter (Box-folder 66/17)
  - Mysterious Billy Smith's Taven (Box-folder 66/18)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) (Box-folder 66/19)
  - National Security Week (Box-folder 66/20)
  - Naturalization Ceremonies (Box-folder 66/21)
  - Neighborhood Improvement Projects (Box-folder 66/22)
  - Neustadter Brothers (Box-folder 66/23)
  - New England Building (Box-folder 66/24)
  - New York Market (Box-folder 66/25)
  - North Pacific Plaza (Box-folder 66/26)
  - Northwest Institute of International Affairs (Box-folder 66/27)
  - Northwest Publishing Co. (Box-folder 66/28)
  - Northwest Steel Co. (Box-folder 66/29)
  - Norwegian Constitution Day Celebrations (Box-folder 66/30)
  - Odd Fellows' Building (Box-folder 66/31)
  - Older Girls' Conference, 1932 April (Box-folder 66/32)
  - One Main Place (Box-folder 66/33)
  - One Pacific Square (Box-folder 66/34)
  - Orbanco Building (Box-folder 66/35)
  - Oregon Building (Box-folder 66/36)
  - Oregon Camera Club (Box-folder 66/37)
  - Oregon District Attorneys Association Convention, 1960 December (Box-folder 66/38)
  - Oregon Diabetics Association (Box-folder 66/39)
  - Oregon Museum of Science & Industry (OMSI) (Box-folder 66/40)
    Formerly called Oregon Memorial Museum of History, Science, and Industry.
  - Oregon Pioneer Savings & Loan Association (Box-folder 66/41)
  - Oregon State Office Building (Box-folder 66/42)
  - Oregon Trail Pageant, 1934 July (Box-folder 66/43)
  - Oregon Trail Savings & Loan Association (Box-folder 66/44)
  - Oregonian 75th Anniversary Celebration, 1925 December (Box-folder 67/1)
  - Oregonian Model Home, 1927 (Box-folder 67/2)
    House constructed on Terwilliger Heights.
  - Orpheum Theater (Box-folder 67/3)
  - Pacific Air Transport Co. (Box-folder 67/4)
  - Pacific Building (Box-folder 67/5)
  - Pacific Light Metal Foundry (Box-folder 67/6)
  - Pacific Livestock International Exposition (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Pacific Northwest Bell (Box-folder 67/8)
  - Pacific Northwest Public Service Co. (Box-folder 67/9)
  - Pacific Roller Canary Club (Box-folder 67/10)
    Also called Portland Canary Club.
  - Pacific Supply Cooperative (Box-folder 67/11)
  - Packard Electric Co. (Box-folder 67/12)
  - Palatine Hill District (Box-folder 67/13)
  - Parent-Child Services, Inc. (Box-folder 67/14)
  - Parent-Teacher Association (Box-folder 67/15)
  - Park Building (Box-folder 67/16)
  - Parkside Center (Box-folder 67/17)
  - Paul Bunyan Coin Convention, 1963 June (Box-folder 67/18)
  - Pearson 4th Avenue Building (Box-folder 67/19)
  - Peck Home (Box-folder 67/20)
    Residence of Grace Peck.
  - Pedestrian Mall (Box-folder 67/21)
    Concept art of a possible pedestrian mall in downtown Portland.
  - Peter Kerr Park (Box-folder 67/22)
  - Peyton-Allan Murder Case (Box-folder 67/23)
  - Philco Radio & Television Corp. (Box-folder 67/24)
    Group photo of Philco distributors. See also People Series for photographs of Philco president Ira Powers.
  - Pi Beta Phi (Box-folder 67/25)
  - Pierce Trailer & Equipment Co. (Box-folder 67/26)
  - Pittock Mansion (Box-folder 67/27)
  - Planned Parenthood (Box-folder 67/28)
  - Plaza Blocks (Box-folder 67/29)
    Collective name for Chapman and Lownsdale Squares.
  - Police Academy (Box-folder 67/30)
    Also called Police Auxiliary School.
  - Police Department (Box-folder 67/31)
  - Police Department - Sunshine Division (Box-folder 67/32)
  - Police Institute on Human Relations and Minority Group Problems Conference, 1958 September (Box-folder 67/33)
  - Pooper-Scooper Law, 1980 December (Box-folder 67/34)
    Headshots of citizens interviewed, captioned with snippets of their opinions regarding new law holding dog owners responsible for cleaning dog waste.
  - Popick's Men's Store (Box-folder 67/35)
  - Poppy Day Sales (Box-folder 67/36)
    Funbdraising event undertaken by auxiliary members of American Legion and Veterans of Foreign Wars.
  - Port of Portland Dredging Projects, 1924 April (Box-folder 67/37)
    Joined pair of photographs depicting dredging at Guilds Lake and the western channel of Swan Island.
  - Portala Study Club (Box-folder 67/38)
  - Porter Building (Box-folder 67/39)
  - Portland Art Museum (1) (Box-folder 68/1)
  - Portland Art Museum (2) (Box-folder 68/2)
  - Portland Art Museum (3) (Box-folder 68/3)
  - Portland Auto Club (Box-folder 68/4)
  - Portland Breakfast Club (Box-folder 68/5)
  - Portland Building (Box-folder 68/6)
  - Portland Casting Club (Box-folder 68/7)
  - Portland Federal Savings & Loan Association (Box-folder 68/8)
  - Portland Federation of Women's Clubs (Box-folder 68/9)
  - Portland Gas & Coke Co. (Box-folder 68/10)
  - Portland Gun Club (Box-folder 68/11)
  - Portland Home Builders Association (Box-folder 68/12)
  - Portland Rose Festival (Box-folder 68/13)
  - Portland State College Extension Center (Box-folder 68/14)
  - Portland Union Stockyards Co. (Box-folder 68/15)
  - Post Offices (Box-folder 68/16)
  - Postal Employees Credit Union (Box-folder 68/17)
  - Powell Grove Cemetery (Box-folder 68/18)
  - Powers Marine Park (Box-folder 68/19)
  - President's Birthday Balls (Box-folder 68/20)
  - President's Club (Box-folder 68/21)
  - Prettyman Home (Box-folder 68/22)
    Residence of Henry W. Prettyman.
  - Project Second Wind (Box-folder 68/23)
  - Providence Nursery (Box-folder 68/24)
    Also called Our Lady of Providence Nursery.
  - Public Comfort Stations (Box-folder 68/25)
    Photograph of stations at the corner of SW 6th and Yamhill.
  - Public Market Building (Box-folder 68/26)
    Served as the offices for the Oregon Journal 1948-1961.
  - Public Service Building (Box-folder 68/27)
  - Public Works Department (Box-folder 68/28)
  - Pythian Sisters (Box-folder 68/29)
  - Quelle Bar (Box-folder 68/30)
  - Radio and TV Stations, Subseries 6
    - KEX (Box-folder 69/1)
    - KGW (Box-folder 69/2)
    - KGW - Hoot Owls (Box-folder 69/3)
    - KLOR (Box-folder 69/4)
    - KOIN (Box-folder 69/5)
    - KPOJ (Box-folder 69/6)
    - KPTV (Box-folder 69/7)
    - KVAN (Box-folder 69/8)
    - KWJJ (Box-folder 69/9)
    - KXL (Box-folder 69/10)
  - Raleigh Green District (Box-folder 69/11)
  - Ramsary Sign Co. Building (Box-folder 69/12)
    Building on Stark Street that formerly served as a Catholic church.
  - Rankin Air Field (Box-folder 69/13)
  - Rankin Building (Box-folder 69/14)
  - Red Lion Motor Inn Hostage Incident, 1979 May 22 (Box-folder 69/15)
  - Redwine Home (Box-folder 69/16)
  - Refugees (Box-folder 69/17)
    Includes photographs of Southeast Asian and Hungarian refugees in Portland.
  - Reicher & Stacy (Box-folder 69/18)
  - "Renovize Portland" Program, 1934 (Box-folder 69/19)
  - Retail Code Authority (Box-folder 69/20)
  - Retail Furtniture Dealers of Oregon Convention, 1933 July (Box-folder 69/21)
  - Retail Merchant Committee Meeting, 1934 April (Box-folder 69/22)
    Based on filing location of photograph and its date, meeting may possibly dealth with "Renovize Portland" program.
  - Ringside Restaurant Hostage Incident, 1980 September (Box-folder 69/23)
  - Rosenblatt's (Box-folder 69/24)
  - Rothchild Home (Box-folder 69/25)
  - "Rough Writers", 1922 September (Box-folder 69/26)
    Group photograph of authors led by George Palmer Putnam who visited Portland.
  - Roy Burnett Motors (Box-folder 69/27)
    Also called Burnett Motors, Inc.
  - St. Johns Day Care Center (Box-folder 69/28)
  - St. Mary's Home for Aged Sisters (Box-folder 69/29)
  - St. Vincent de Paul Day Care Center (Box-folder 69/30)
  - Salvation Army (Box-folder 69/31)
  - Schools (1) (Box-folder 69/32)
  - Schools (2) (Box-folder 69/33)
  - Schools - "City School Sketchbook Series", 1931 (Box-folder 70/1)
    Photographs taken for a series of stories on Portland schools.
  - Scott Building (Box-folder 70/2)
    Formerly called Buchanan Building.
  - Scott Home (Box-folder 70/3)
    Residence of Bishop Scott.
  - Scottish Rite Cathedral (Box-folder 70/4)
  - Sears, Roebuck & Co. (Box-folder 70/5)
  - Selling Building (Box-folder 70/6)
  - Sherlock Building (Box-folder 70/7)
  - Shriners (Box-folder 70/8)
  - Sidewalk Cabbage, 1973 September (Box-folder 70/9)
    Image of a cabbage that sprouted and grew at SW 5th and Oak Streets.
  - Skidmore Art Colony (Box-folder 70/10)
  - Skidmore House (Box-folder 70/11)
  - Skyline Memorial Gardens (Box-folder 70/12)
  - South Auditorium Urban Renewal Area (Box-folder 70/13)
  - Spalding Building (Box-folder 70/14)
  - Stadium Freeway (Box-folder 70/15)
    Contains 1962 image of model of proposed thouroughfare.
  - Standard Insurance Co. (Box-folder 70/16)
    Mostly photographs of Standard Plaza.
  - Statues (Box-folder 70/17)
  - Stowbridge Building (Box-folder 70/18)
  - Strahan Home (Box-folder 70/19)
    Residence of attorney Claude Strahan.
  - Streets (Box-folder 70/20)
    Includes images of Burnside Street, Front Street, SE Grand Avenue, Leif Erickson Drive, SW Stark Street, Westover Terrace, and Willamette Boulevard.
  - Streets - Canyon Road Improvements, 1927-1931 (Box-folder 70/21)
  - Strikes (Box-folder 70/22)
  - Sullivan Gulch Freeway (Box-folder 70/23)
  - Swain's Boarding House (Box-folder 70/24)
    Located on 5th and Morrison; site later became the Meier & Frank Building.
  - Swan Island Airport (Box-folder 70/25)
  - Sylvan Westgate Building (Box-folder 70/26)
  - Taylor Building (Box-folder 70/27)
  - Telephone Building (Box-folder 70/28)
  - Thomas Mann Building (Box-folder 70/29)
  - Thompson Home (Box-folder 70/30)
    Residence of R. R. Thompson
  - Thurlow Glove Factory (Box-folder 70/31)
  - Times Building (Box-folder 70/32)
  - Town Hall, 1968 September (Box-folder 70/33)
    New name for former Finnish Workers Association Hall
  - Tree-Planting Ceremony, 1932 April 8 (Box-folder 70/34)
    Two images related to tree-planting ceremony done in honor of pupils who won an essay contest on the life of George Washington.
  - Tri-Met (Box-folder 70/35)
  - Union Gospel Mission (Box-folder 70/36)
  - United Carriage Co. (Box-folder 70/37)
  - United Cerebral Palsy (Box-folder 70/38)
  - United States Customs House (Box-folder 71/1)
  - United States District Court (Box-folder 71/2)
  - United States Revolution Bicentennial Celebrations (Box-folder 71/3)
  - US Bancorp Tower (Box-folder 71/4)
  - US Bank Plaza (Box-folder 71/5)
  - US Daughters of 1812 (Box-folder 71/6)
  - Verseweavers (Box-folder 71/7)
    Poets group.
  - Veterans' Employment Office (Box-folder 71/8)
  - Village at Lovejoy Fountain (Box-folder 71/9)
  - Vines Building (Box-folder 71/10)
  - Volunteers of America (Box-folder 71/11)
    Contains images of day nurseries run by Volunteers of America.
  - Waco Air Taxi (Box-folder 71/12)
  - Waddle's Drive-In Restaurant (Box-folder 71/13)
  - Washington Cooperative Farmers Association Mill (Box-folder 71/14)
    Located at Mock's Bottom.
  - Washington Park (Box-folder 71/15)
  - Washington Park Zoo (Box-folder 71/16)
  - Washington Park Zoo - Elephants (1) (Box-folder 71/17)
  - Washington Park Zoo - Elephants (2) (Box-folder 71/18)
  - Waverly Baby Home (Box-folder 71/19)
  - Wentworth & Irwin (Box-folder 71/20)
  - West Coast Air Transport Co. (Box-folder 71/21)
  - Western Association of Art Museums Conference, 1966 October 14 (Box-folder 71/22)
  - Western Cooperage Co. (Box-folder 71/23)
  - Westmoreland Union Manor (Box-folder 71/24)
  - Wilcox Building (Box-folder 71/25)
  - Wilcox Home (Box-folder 71/26)
    Residence of T. B. Wilcox.
  - Willamette National Cemetery (Box-folder 71/27)
    See also: Portland - Memorial Day Celebrations.
  - Women of Woodcraft Building (Box-folder 71/28)
  - Woodlark Building (Box-folder 71/29)
  - Woodward & Clarke Building (Box-folder 71/30)
  - Worcester Block (Box-folder 71/31)
  - Worcester Building (Box-folder 71/32)
  - Wortman Home (Box-folder 71/33)
    Residence of H. C. Wortman
  - Yeon Building (Box-folder 71/34)
  - Young's Gown Shop (Box-folder 71/35)
  - Young Men's Christian Associaiton (YMCA) (Box-folder 71/36)
  - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) (Box-folder 71/37)
- Washington State, 1889-1984; Series D
  - Aberdeen (Box-folder 72/1)
  - Mt. Adams (Box-folder 72/2)
  - Ape Cave (Box-folder 72/3)
  - Mt. Baker (Box-folder 72/4)
  - Bangor (Box-folder 72/5)
  - Battle Ground (Box-folder 72/6)
  - Battle Ground State Park (Box-folder 72/7)
  - Beacon Rock (Box-folder 72/8)
  - Bellingham (Box-folder 72/9)
  - Benton-Franklin County Fair (Box-folder 72/10)
  - Blaine (Box-folder 72/11)
  - Blakely Island (Box-folder 72/12)
  - Blue Lake (Box-folder 72/13)
  - Bremerton (Box-folder 72/14)
  - Bridges (Box-folder 72/15)
    Includes photos of bridges over the Cowlitz River, Deception Pass Brodge, Heissen Bridge, and bridges in the Pasco-Kennewick area.
  - Hood Canal Floating Bridge (Box-folder 72/16)
  - Lake Washington Floating Bridge (Box-folder 72/17)
  - Tacoma Narrows Bridge (Box-folder 72/18)
  - Camas (Box-folder 72/19)
  - Camp Bonneville (Box-folder 72/20)
  - Camp Columbia (Box-folder 72/21)
  - Campy Murray (Box-folder 72/22)
  - Cape Disappointment (Box-folder 72/23)
  - Cascade Tunnel (Box-folder 72/24)
  - Cathlamet (Box-folder 72/25)
  - Centralia (Box-folder 72/26)
  - Centralia Steam Electric Project (Box-folder 72/27)
  - Charles Mattson Kidnapping Case (Box-folder 72/28)
    Mattson was taken from his Tacoma home in December 1936, and found dead January 1937.
  - Chehalis (Box-folder 72/29)
  - Lake Chelan (Box-folder 72/30)
  - Cherry Point Refinery (Box-folder 72/31)
  - Church Mountain (Box-folder 72/32)
  - Clamarama (Box-folder 72/33)
    Event held between Grays Harbor and lower Quinault River.
  - Clark County (Box-folder 72/34)
  - Clark County Fair (Box-folder 72/35)
  - Coast (Box-folder 73/1)
  - College Place (Box-folder 73/2)
  - Columbia Basin Project (Box-folder 73/3)
  - Columbia River Truck-Barge Transportation, 1932 August (Box-folder 73/4)
    Photographs demonstrating the use of trucks and barges to transport wheat on the Washington side of the Columbia River.
  - Cougar (Box-folder 73/5)
  - Cowlitz Pioneers & Descendants Association (Box-folder 73/6)
  - Cowlitz River (Box-folder 73/7)
  - Crystal Mountain, Inc. (Box-folder 73/8)
    Restauarant located on top of Crystal Mountain with a view of Mt. Rainier.
  - Dallesport (Box-folder 73/9)
  - Dams (Box-folder 73/10)
    Includes images of Albeni Falls Dam, Des Chutes Dam, Diablo Dam, Little Goose Dam, Merwin Dam, Mossyrock Dam, Rock Island Dam, and Yale Dam.
  - Ariel Dam (Box-folder 73/11)
  - Grand Coulee Dam (1) (Box-folder 73/12)
  - Grand Coulee Dam (2) (Box-folder 73/13)
  - Swift Dam (Box-folder 73/14)
  - Wanapum Dam (Box-folder 73/15)
  - Deception Pass (Box-folder 73/16)
  - Destruction Island Lighthouse (Box-folder 73/17)
  - Earthquakes (Box-folder 73/18)
  - Ellensburg (Box-folder 73/19)
  - Elma (Box-folder 73/20)
  - Everett (Box-folder 73/21)
  - Fires (1) (Box-folder 73/22)
  - Fires (2) (Box-folder 73/23)
  - Floods (1) (Box-folder 74/1)
  - Floods (2) (Box-folder 74/2)
  - Forest Fires (Box-folder 74/3)
  - Fort Borst (Box-folder 74/4)
  - Fort Canby Lighthouse (Box-folder 74/5)
  - Fort Casey (Box-folder 74/6)
  - Fort Columbia (Box-folder 74/7)
  - Fort Lawton (Box-folder 74/8)
  - Fort Lewis (Box-folder 74/9)
  - Fort Simcoe (Box-folder 74/10)
  - Frankfort (Box-folder 74/11)
  - Friday Harbor (Box-folder 74/12)
  - Frostly Lake (Box-folder 74/13)
  - Glacier Peak (Box-folder 74/14)
  - Goldendale (Box-folder 74/15)
  - Grand Coulee Lake (Box-folder 74/16)
  - Hanford Nuclear Power Plant (1) (Box-folder 74/17)
  - Hanford Nuclear Power Plant (2) (Box-folder 74/18)
  - Harmony Falls (Box-folder 74/19)
  - Hazel Dell (Box-folder 74/20)
  - Highways (Box-folder 74/21)
    Includes images of Highway No. 8, Elma-Grand Mound Highway, and Evergreen Highway.
  - Hood Canal (Box-folder 74/22)
  - Hoquiam (Box-folder 74/23)
  - Ilwaco (Box-folder 74/24)
  - Kennewick (Box-folder 74/25)
  - Kennewick Gas Fields (Box-folder 74/26)
  - La Center (Box-folder 74/27)
  - Lackamas Park (Box-folder 74/28)
  - Landslides (Box-folder 75/1)
  - Larson Air Base (Box-folder 75/2)
  - Leavenworth (Box-folder 75/3)
  - Lewis River (Box-folder 75/4)
  - Lewisville Park (Box-folder 75/5)
  - Logging Garden (Box-folder 75/6)
    Unique logging-themed garden of Mr. and Mrs. Joe Brandt located in New London, north of Hoquiam.
  - Long Beach (Box-folder 75/7)
  - Longview (Box-folder 75/8)
  - Longview - Homesteads (Box-folder 75/9)
  - Maryhill (1) (Box-folder 75/10)